# **Vernal Liu**

## Contact

### Address:

Shenyang, Liaoning, China

#### **Email:**

covernal@hotmail.com

## Skype:

vernalco

## Linkedin:

Vernal Liu on Linkedin

# Languages

English Chinese

# Skill Highlights

- Angular.js
- React.js
- Bootstrap
- Laravel/PHP
- Mean.js
- Python/Django

# Summary

Full-stack web developer specializing in front end and back end development. Experienced with all stages of the development cycle for dynamic web projects. Well-versed in numerous programming languages and frameworks including HTML5, PHP, JavaScript, Angular.js, React.js, Typescript, Laravel, Express.js. Strong background in project management and customer relations.

## Experience

## Lead Developer, Hestec internetdiensten - 2015 to 2017

- iOS, Android mobile app using IONIC
- ASP.NET backend server
- SOAP API

### Top Web & Mobile Freelancer, Freelancer.com - 2012 to 2018

- Completed 111+ projects successfully.
- 111 + of 5.0 reviews from happy clients.

## Lead Developer, Astute Technology Limited - 2017 to 2018

• iOS, Android mobile app using IONIC

### Co-worker, IKEO - 2016 to 2017

- Designed IKEO solution
- Built API service, mobile apps

#### goOnCommunication, Media4You - 2017 to 2018

- Designed server architecture based on XMPP
- Built XMPP server using Node.js & Mean.js
- Lead mobile framework for consuming service.
- Auto-deploy chat servers using docker image.

## Reservations.com, Reservation - 2016 to 2017

- Built web pages using Angular, Bootstrap
- SEO on the web site.

## Ethereum wallet, IDTEQ-2018 to 2019

- Built Ethereum token
- Built website using React, CSS3 animation.

# Education

Master degree: Shenyang University of Technology - 2007